dailygram.com 2019-04-30

# Privacy Policy » Dailygram ... The Business Network

Dailygram's Privacy Policy. 

Date of last revision: May 24, 2018.   

1\. Introduction 

Scope. This privacy policy covers all of Dailygram. It does not, however, apply to entities that Dailygram does not own or control, such as applications and websites using our platform. By using or accessing Dailygram, you agree to our privacy practices outlined here. 

Safe Harbor. Dailygram also complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. As part of our participation in the Safe Harbor, we agree to resolve all disputes you have with us in connection with our policies and practices through TRUSTe. We will also provide initial responses to access requests within a reasonable period of time. 

No information from children under age 13. If you are under age 13, please do not attempt to register for Dailygram or provide any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us through our contact page. 

Gender and Birth Date. In addition to name and email address, we require you to provide your gender and birth date during the registration process. We ask for your date of birth to verify that you are 13 or older, and so that we can better limit your access to content and advertisements that are not age appropriate. Because your date of birth and gender are required, you cannot delete them. You can, however, edit your profile to hide all (or part) of such fields from other users. 

Parental participation. We strongly recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet and we encourage parents to teach their children about safe internet use practices. Materials to help parents talk to their children about safe internet use can be found on our help pages.   

2\. Information We Collect and How We Use It 

Information you provide to us about yourself. When you sign up for Dailygram you provide us with your name, email, gender, and birth date. During the registration process we give you the opportunity to connect with your friends, schools, and employers. You will also be able to add a picture of yourself. In some cases we may ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide specific services to you. Once you register you can provide other information about yourself by connecting with, for example, your current city, hometown, family, relationships, networks, activities, interests, and places. You can also provide personal information about yourself, such as your political and religious views. 

Content. One of the primary reasons people use Dailygram is to share content with others. Examples include when you update your status, upload or take a photo, upload or record a video, share a link, create an event or a group, make a comment, write something on someone's chat board, write a note, or send someone a message. If you do not want us to store metadata associated with content you share on Dailygram (such as photos), please remove the metadata before uploading the content. 

Transactional Information. We may retain the details of transactions or payments you make on Dailygram. If you do not want us to store your payment source account number, you can remove it using your payments page. 

Friend Information. We offer tools to help you upload your friends' addresses so that you can find your friends on Dailygram, and invite your contacts who do not have Dailygram accounts to join. If you do not want us to store this information, visit the help pages. If you give us your password to retrieve those contacts, we will not store your password after you have uploaded your contacts' information. 

Site activity information. We keep track of some of the actions you take on Dailygram, such as adding connections (including joining a group or adding a friend), creating a photo album, sending a gift, poking another user, indicating you like a post, attending an event, or connecting with an application. In some cases you are also taking an action when you provide information or content to us. For example, if you share a video, in addition to storing the actual content you uploaded, we might log the fact that you shared it. 

Access Device and Browser Information. When you access Dailygram from a computer, mobile phone, or other device, we may collect information from that device about your browser type, location, and IP address, as well as the pages you visit. 

Cookie Information. We use "cookies" (small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other device) to make Dailygram easier to use, to make our advertising better, and to protect both you and Dailygram. For example, we use them to store your login ID (but never your password) to make it easier for you to login whenever you come back to Dailygram. We also use them to confirm that you are logged into Dailygram, and to know when you are interacting with Dailygram Platform applications and websites, our widgets and Share buttons, and our advertisements. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases that may impact your ability to use Dailygram. 

Dailygram Communities. We do not own or operate the applications or websites that you use through Dailygram Communities (such as games and utilities). Whenever you connect with a Community application or website, we will receive information from them, including information about actions you take. In some cases, in order to personalize the process of connecting, we may receive a limited amount of information even before you connect with the application or website. 

Information from other websites. We may institute programs with advertising partners and other websites in which they share information with us: 

• We may ask advertisers to tell us how our users responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other users who didn't see the ads acted on their site). This data sharing, commonly known as "conversion tracking," helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see.   
• We may receive information about whether or not you've seen or interacted with certain ads on other sites in order to measure the effectiveness of those ads. 

Information from other users. We may collect information about you from other Dailygram users, such as when a friend tags you in a photo, video, or place, provides friend details, or indicates a relationship with you.   

3\. Sharing information on Dailygram 

This section explains how your privacy settings work, and how your information is shared on Dailygram. You should always consider your privacy settings before sharing information on Dailygram. 

Name and Profile Picture. Dailygram is designed to make it easy for you to find and connect with others. For this reason, your name and profile picture do not have privacy settings. If you are uncomfortable with sharing your profile picture, you should delete it (or not add one). You can also control who can find you when searching on Dailygram or on public search engines using the available privacy setting. 

Contact Information. Your contact information settings control (available when customizing your privacy settings) who can contact you on Dailygram, and who can see your contact information such as your email and phone number(s). Remember that none of this information is required except for your email address, and you do not have to share your email address with anyone. 

Personal Information. Your personal information settings control who can see your personal information, such as your religious and political views, if you choose to add them. We recommend that you share this information using the friends' settings. 

Posts by you. You can select a privacy setting for every post you make using the privacy settings on our site. Whether you are uploading a photo or posting a status update, you can control exactly who can see it at the time you create it. 

Information that you share publicly is available to everyone (like your name, profile picture, and connections). Such information may, for example, be accessed by everyone on the Internet (including people not logged into Dailygram), be indexed by third party search engines, and be imported, exported, distributed, and redistributed by us and others without privacy limitations. Such information may also be associated with you, including your name and profile picture, even outside of Dailygram, such as on public search engines and when you visit other sites on the internet. The default privacy setting for certain types of information you post on Dailygram is set to "everyone." You can review and change the default settings in your privacy settings. If you delete "everyone" content that you posted on Dailygram, we will remove it from your Dailygram profile, but have no control over its use outside of Dailygram. 

Minors. We reserve the right to add special protections for minors (such as to provide them with an age-appropriate experience) and place restrictions on the ability of adults to share and connect with minors, recognizing this may provide minors a more limited experience on Dailygram   

4\. Information You Share With Third Parties 

Dailygram Communities. As mentioned above, we do not own or operate the applications or websites that use Dailygram Communities. That means that when you use those applications and websites you are making your Dailygram information available to someone other than Dailygram. Prior to allowing them to access any information about you, we require them to agree to terms that limit their use of your information and we use technical measures to ensure that they only obtain authorized information. 

Connecting with an Application or Website. When you connect with an application or website it will have access to General Information about you. The term General Information includes your and your friends' names, profile pictures, gender, user IDs, connections, and any content shared using the Everyone privacy setting. We may also make information about the location of your computer or access device and your age available to applications and websites in order to help them implement appropriate security measures and control the distribution of age-appropriate content. If the application or website wants to access any other data, it will have to ask for your permission. We give you tools to control how your information is shared with applications and websites that use Communities. For example, you can block all community applications and websites completely or block specific applications from accessing your information by visiting your privacy setting or the specific application's "About" page. You can also use your privacy settings to limit which of your information is available to "everyone".   

You should always review the policies of third party applications and websites to make sure you are comfortable with the ways in which they use information you share with them. We do not guarantee that they will follow our rules. If you find an application or website that violates our rules, you should report the violation to us on this help page and we will take action as necessary. 

Pre-Approved Third-Party Websites and Applications. In order to provide you with useful social experiences off of Dailygram, we occasionally need to provide General Information about you to pre-approved third party websites and applications at the time you visit them (if you are still logged in to Dailygram). Similarly, when one of your friends visits a pre-approved website or application, it will receive General Information about you so you and your friend can be connected on that website as well (if you also have an account with that website). In these cases we require these websites and applications to go through an approval process, and to enter into separate agreements designed to protect your privacy. For example, these agreements include provisions relating to the access and deletion of your General Information, along with your ability to opt-out of the experience being offered. You can disable instant personalization on all pre-approved websites and applications using your Applications and Websites privacy setting. You can also block a particular pre-approved website or application by clicking an appropriate button when you visit that application or website. In addition, if you log out of Dailygram before visiting a pre-approved application or website, it will not be able to access your information. 

Exporting Information. You (and those you make your information available to) may use tools like RSS feeds, mobile phone address book applications, or copy and paste functions, to capture, export (and in some cases, import) information from Dailygram, including your information and information about you. For example, if you share your phone number with your friends, they may use third party applications to sync that information with the address book on their mobile phone. 

Advertisements. Sometimes the advertisers who present ads on Dailygram use technological methods to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. You may also use your browser cookie settings to limit or prevent the placement of cookies by advertising networks. Dailygram does not share personally identifiable information with advertisers unless we get your permission. 

Links. When you click on links on Dailygram you may leave our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, and we encourage you to read their privacy statements.   

5\. How We Use Your Information 

We use the information we collect to try to provide a safe, efficient, and customized experience. Specifically: 

To manage the service. We use the information we collect to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customer support. We use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities, and to enforce our Statement of Rights and Responsibilities. We also use a variety of technological systems to detect and address anomalous activity and screen content to prevent abuse such as spam. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users. 

To contact you. We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time. You may opt out of all communications except essential updates on your account notifications page. We may include content you see on Dailygram in the emails we send to you. 

To serve personalized advertising to you. We don't share your information with advertisers without your consent. (An example of consent would be if you asked us to provide your shipping address to an advertiser to receive a free sample.) We allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements and we may use any of the non-personally identifiable attributes we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. For example, we might use your interest in sports to show you ads for tennis equipment, but we do not tell the advertiser who you are. You can see the criteria advertisers may select by visiting our advertising page. Even though we do not share your information with advertisers without your consent, when you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement there is a possibility that the advertiser may place a cookie in your browser and note that it meets the criteria they selected. 

To serve social ads. We occasionally pair advertisements we serve with relevant information we have about you and your friends to make advertisements more interesting and more tailored to you and your friends. For example, if you connect with your favorite band's page, we may display your name and profile photo next to an advertisement for that page that is displayed to your friends. We only share the personally identifiable information visible in the social ad with the friend who can see the ad. You can opt out of having your information used in social ads on this help page. 

To make suggestions. We use your information, including the addresses you import through our contact importers, to make suggestions to you and other users on Dailygram. For example, if another user imports the same email address as you do, we may suggest that you add each other as friends. Similarly, if one of your friends uploads a picture of you, we may suggest that your friend tag you in the picture. We do this by comparing your friend's pictures to information we've put together from the photos you've been tagged in. We may also suggest that you use certain tools and features based on what your friends have used. You can control whether we suggest that another user add you as a friend through your "search for you on Dailygram" privacy setting. You can control whether we suggest that another user tag you in a photo by clicking customize from your privacy settings. 

To help your friends find you. We allow other users to use contact information they have about you, such as your email address, to find you, including through contact importers and search. You can prevent other users from using your email address to find you using the search section of your privacy settings. 

Downloadable Software. Certain downloadable software applications and applets that we offer, such as our browser toolbars and photo uploaders, transmit data to us. We may not make a formal disclosure if we believe our collection of and use of the information is the obvious purpose of the application, such as the fact that we receive photos when you use our photo uploader. If we believe it is not obvious that we are collecting or using such information, we will make a disclosure to you the first time you provide the information to us so that you can decide whether you want to use that feature. 

Memorializing Accounts. If we are notified that a user is deceased, we may memorialize the user's account. In such cases we restrict profile access to confirmed friends, and allow friends and family to write on the user's chat space in remembrance. We may close an account if we receive a formal request from the user's next of kin or other proper legal request to do so.   

6\. How We Share Information 

Dailygram is about sharing information with others — friends and people in your communities — while providing you with privacy settings that you can use to restrict other users from accessing some of your information. We share your information with third parties when we believe the sharing is permitted by you, reasonably necessary to offer our services, or when legally required to do so. For example: 

When you make a payment. When you enter into transactions with others or make payments on Dailygram, we will share transaction information with only those third parties necessary to complete the transaction. We will require those third parties to agree to respect the privacy of your information. 

When you invite a friend to join. When you ask us to invite a friend to join Dailygram, we will send your friend a message on your behalf using your name. The invitation may also contain information about other users your friend might know. You can see who has accepted your invitations, send reminders, and delete your friends' email addresses on your invite history page. If your friend does not want us to keep their information, we will also remove it at their request by using this help page. 

When you choose to share your information with marketers. You may choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers that are not associated with Dailygram through on-site offers. This is entirely at your discretion and we will not provide your information to these marketers without your consent. 

To help your friends find you. By default, we make certain information you have posted to your profile available in search results on Dailygram to help your friends find you. However, you can control who can see some of this information, as well as who can find you in searches, through your privacy settings. We also partner with email and instant messaging providers to help their users identify which of their contacts are Dailygram users, so that we can promote Dailygram to those users. 

To give search engines access to publicly available information. We generally limit search engines' access to our site. We may allow them to access information set to the "everyone" setting (along with your name and profile picture) and your profile information that is visible to everyone. You can change the visibility of some of your profile information using the customize section of your privacy settings. 

To help improve or promote our service. Sometimes we share aggregated information with third parties to help improve or promote our service. But we only do so in such a way that no individual user can be identified or linked to any specific action or information. 

To provide you with services. We may provide information to service providers that help us bring you the services we offer. For example, we may use third parties to help host our website, send out email updates about Dailygram, remove repetitive information from our user lists, process payments, or provide search results or links (including sponsored links). These service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time, but when this occurs we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections to limit their use of that information to helping us provide the service. 

To advertise our services. We may ask advertisers outside of Dailygram to display ads promoting our services. We may ask them to deliver those ads based on the presence of a cookie, but in doing so will not share any other information with the advertiser. 

To offer joint services. We may provide services jointly with other companies, such as the classifieds service in the Dailygram Marketplace. If you use these services, we may share your information to facilitate that service. However, we will identify the partner and present the joint service provider's privacy policy to you before you use that service. 

To respond to legal requests and prevent harm. We may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests (including criminal and civil matters) if we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law. This may include respecting requests from jurisdictions outside of the United States where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law under the local laws in that jurisdiction, apply to users from that jurisdiction, and are consistent with generally accepted international standards. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect ourselves and you from people violating our policies. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts or other government entities. 

Transfer in the Event of Sale or Change of Control. If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the service can continue to operate. In such a case, your information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.   

7\. How You Can Change or Remove Information 

Editing your profile. You may change or remove your profile information at any time by going to your profile page and clicking "Edit My Profile." Information will be updated immediately. 

Delete uploaded contacts. You can delete the email addresses of friends you have invited to join Dailygram on your invite history page. 

Deactivating or deleting your account. If you want to stop using your account you may deactivate it or delete it. When you deactivate an account, no user will be able to see it, but it will not be deleted. We save your profile information (connections, photos, etc.) in case you later decide to reactivate your account. Many users deactivate their accounts for temporary reasons and in doing so are asking us to maintain their information until they return to Dailygram. You will still have the ability to reactivate your account and restore your profile in its entirety. When you delete an account, it is permanently deleted from Dailygram. You should only delete your account if you are certain you never want to reactivate it. You may deactivate your account on your account settings page or delete your account by visiting your account settings page. 

Limitations on removal. Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users. Additionally, we may retain certain information to prevent identity theft and other misconduct even if deletion has been requested. If you have given third party applications or websites access to your information, they may retain your information to the extent permitted under their terms of service or privacy policies. But they will no longer be able to access the information through our website after you disconnect from them. 

Backup copies. Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies for up to 90 days, but will not be available to others. 

Non-user contact information. If a user provides your email address to us, and you are not a Dailygram user but you want us to delete your address, you can do so on this help page. However, that request will only apply to addresses we have at the time of the request and not to any addresses that users provide to us later.   

8\. How We Protect Information 

Risks inherent in sharing information. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you share your information. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We cannot ensure that information you share on Dailygram will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures on Dailygram. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up to date antivirus software. 

Report Violations. You should report any security violations to us through the help page.   

9\. Other Terms 

Changes. We may change this Privacy Policy pursuant to the procedures outlined elsewhere on Dailygram. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by publication here. If the changes are material, we will provide you additional, prominent notice as appropriate under the circumstances. 

10\. California Residents: your California Privacy Rights

We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their goods or services to you unless you first agree to such disclosure. If you have any questions regarding this policy, or would like to change your preferences, you may contact us at the address listed below.

11\. Contact

You may contact us online concerning our Privacy Policy (by using the Contact Us link below), or you may write to us at the following address:

Dailygram

P.O. Box 4381

Milton, Florida 32572

USA  

Consent to Collection and Processing in the United States. By using Dailygram, you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.
